So whether you're in a restaurant or not there are some common ways to ask for things and we've looked
因此，无论您是否在餐厅，都有一些常见的询问方式，我们已经看过
at a couple of these phrases before.
在这些短语之前。
So some of this will be review.
所以其中一些将被审查。
But we do want to talk about a couple of key phrases especially for being in a restaurant.
但我们确实想谈谈几个关键短语，尤其是在餐厅里。
We can say of course I'd like you can say this on an airplane.
我们当然可以说我希望你可以在飞机上这样说。
You can say this in a restaurant.
你可以在餐厅里这样说。
You can say this to your friend do you need anything.
你可以对你的朋友说你需要什么。
Yeah I'd like a glass of water that's a little bit too polite.
是的，我想要一杯有点太客气的水。
In some situations but especially if you're on an airplane if you're at a restaurant.
在某些情况下，特别是如果你在飞机上，如果你在餐馆里。
Very very common.
非常非常常见。
I'll have you go to Starbucks and you want to order a coffee.
我让你去星巴克，你想点一杯咖啡。
You could say I'll have a cappuccino.
你可以说我要一杯卡布奇诺。
I'll have a latte.
我要一杯拿铁。
I'll have an Americano whatever you want to have.
我要一杯美式咖啡，你想吃什么都行。
Or you can make it a question.
或者你可以提出一个问题。
Could I please have that question.
请问我可以问这个问题吗？
Could I please have an Americano.
请给我一杯美式咖啡。
Or could I please have a menu.
或者我可以请一个菜单。
Could I please have diet coke whatever you want to say.
你想说什么，我可以请你喝健怡可乐吗？
Very common as well.
也很常见。
Sometimes we may want to express a little bit less certainty and so we might say I guess I guess I'll
有时我们可能想表达一些不太确定的东西，所以我们可能会说我猜我猜我会
take this is just a way to make it sound a little bit more casual perhaps.
采取这只是一种让它听起来更随意的方式。
I guess I'll take the chicken burrito chicken burrito.
我想我会吃鸡肉卷饼鸡肉卷饼。
Yeah sometimes it also shows that you're not totally confident about your choice.
是的，有时这也表明你对自己的选择并不完全有信心。
Can I get.
我能得到吗。
Can.
能。
Can I get a glass of red wine please.
请给我一杯红酒好吗？
And this is also a question Can I get a glass of red wine please.
这也是一个问题，请给我一杯红酒。
OK.
好的。
And then finally I think I'll order.
最后我想我会订购。
I think I'll order the chocolate cake for dessert.
我想我会点巧克力蛋糕做甜点。
I think I'll order the chocolate cake.
我想我会点巧克力蛋糕。
So these are basically if you know how to use these well these are the most common phrases for asking
所以这些基本上是如果你知道如何很好地使用这些是最常见的询问短语
for what you want.
为了你想要的。
If you stop this lesson right now stop watching at least you have this.
如果你现在停止这节课，至少你有这个停止观看。
These are the basics but we are going to go into how they're used in context remember we do things in
这些是基础知识，但我们将讨论它们在上下文中的使用方式，记住我们在
context and the reason that we do everything in context in this situation with real examples is because
上下文以及我们在这种情况下使用真实示例在上下文中做所有事情的原因是因为
just knowing one sentence makes it hard to actually then use because you're not sure if that one sentence
只知道一句话就很难实际使用，因为你不确定那句话是否
exactly fits right.
完全合适。
So when we look at examples you can get a better feeling for how these phrases are used.
因此，当我们查看示例时，您可以更好地了解这些短语的使用方式。
So we'll go through a real situation ordering in a restaurant and leading up to ordering.
因此，我们将通过一个真实的情况在餐厅点餐并进行点餐。
So let's let's do that.
所以让我们这样做吧。